（忆往昔）
给我抓超自然生物 要在食物链顶端的
Bring me creatures. Aim high on the food chain.
无论我们抓到什么 最后都送到这来
Whatever we bag… ends up there.
他在这折磨他们 审问他们
That's where he tortures them, interrogates them …
我真的就不知道了
I don't really know.
- 我不是你的雇员 - 你们当然是
- We ain't your employees. - Of course you are!
礼物包里是什么
What's in the gift bag?
- 是你 - 不可能
- You are. - Not possible.
你的遗骸并没有藏得那么好
You didn't hide your bones as well as you should have.
她是谁 这个叫夏娃的婊子
Who is she, this Eve bitch?
我们所有人的母亲
The mother of all of us,
还是你们所有人的末日
and the end of all of you.
凤凰的灰烬可以烧掉万物之母
The ashes of a phoenix can burn the mother.
1861年
"1861,
桑勒斯 怀俄明州
"Sunrise, wyoming.
今天枪杀了一只凤凰
"Gun killed a phoenix today.
留下一堆阴燃的灰烬
Left a pile of smoldering ash."
- 谁的枪 - 科尔特的
- Whose gun? - CoIt's.
我们穿越回到过去
We hop back in time,
找到萨穆埃尔·科尔特
we join up with Samuel Colt,
我们猎杀那只凤凰
We hunt the phoenix,
然后带上灰烬回来
and then haul its ashes back home.
- 那是我想的那东西吗 - 凤凰的灰烬
- Is that what I think it is? - Ashes of a phoenix.
你知道这意味着什么吗
You know what this means?
我们要和她开战了
We take the fight to her.
（如今）
我是认真的 没开玩笑
I'm serious. I'm serious.
那真的太宰人了 伙计
That was way overpriced, dude.
在我家乡 啤酒就三块钱一瓶
Back where I'm from, okay, it was like $3 a beer.
好吧 那下次我请客
Okay. Then, I'm buying next time.
我没说谎 真的没开玩笑
I'm not even lying. I'm not even joking at all.
嘿
Hey.
天使下凡了啊
Heaven must be missing an angel.
我想她喜欢我
I think she likes me.
好了 自恋狂 走了
Okay, Fabio. Let's … let's go.
你没事吧 小姐
Are you okay, miss?
我很好
I'm perfect.
我是说 那是血吗
I mean, is … is that blood?
是 我想是的
Yes, I suppose it is.
你真的没事吧
You sure you're all right?
嘿 怎么回事
Hey, what the hell?!
我送给他了一份礼物
I gave him a gift.
快 咱们走吧
Come on, man. Let's get out of here.
[邪恶力量 第6季第19集]
嘿 你怎么样
Hey. How you doing?
五发子弹 就是这样
Five shells … that's how I'm doing.
你知道的
Well, you know,
比起上周 这已经算不错了
It's a hell of a lot more than we had last week.
也许
Maybe.
什么意思
Meaning?
就是我刚才出了个小意外
Meaning I just had myself a little mishap a few minutes ago,
还有 看
And, uh … well, here, look.
这东西应该能烧死夏娃
This stuff is supposed to burn the bejesus out of Eve.
可我涂上它屁感觉都没有
It doesn't even give me a sunburn.
传说应该有用的
The lore says it works.
你也会说是「传说」
That's always reliable.
也许它就像…
Well, you know what? M-maybe it's like …
也许就像铁或者银
maybe it's like iron or silver, you know?
伤害他们 不会伤害我们
Hurts them and not us?
可能吧 但倒是对我们很有好处
Maybe, but a fat lot of good it does us.
直到我们找到那个婊子
until we find the bitch.
我在找 但是我想
I'm looking, but I'm thinking.
可能你是时候来次召唤了
maybe it's time you made a call.
为什么每次都是我召唤呢
Why's it always got to be me that makes the call, huh?
小卡又不是我的跟屁虫
It's not like Cass lives in my ass.
那家伙忙着呢
The dude's busy.
小卡 别跟我屁股后头
Cass, get out of my ass!
我从没在你的…
I was never in your …
你们找夏娃的工作有什么进展了吗
Have you made any progress in locating Eve?
其实 我们正想问你呢
Well, we were gonna ask you about that.
我找过 但是她能躲开我
I've looked, but she's hidden from me.
她躲掉了所有的天使
She's hidden from all angels.
太好了
Awesome.
你知道 其实我们就需要一个内应
You know, what we really need is an inside man.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
一个有爪子有同情心的家伙
Something with claws and sympathy.
是说一个友好的怪物吗
Like a friendly monster?
现在这样的越来越少了 你说呢
Those are in short supply these days, don't you think?
是 但是我们见过一两个 对吗
Sure, but we've met one or two, right?
可能
Maybe.
也许我们能找到一个
So, maybe we can find one.
丽诺尔 等等
Lenore. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
嘿 丽诺尔 停下
Hey, hey. Lenore, stop.
听着 我们很高兴见到你
Look, we're happy you're here.
我叫丽诺尔 我不会伤害你们
My name's Lenore. I'm not gonna hurt you.
很久没见了
It's been a long time.
你还记得我们吗
You remember us?
记得
I remember.
你们的猎人朋友差点杀了我
Your hunter friend almost killed me.
那么 如果这能让你舒服些
Well, if it makes you feel any better,
他后来变成了吸血鬼
uh, he turned into a vampire,
最后我砍掉了他的头
and I chopped his head off.
用铁丝网 超赞
Yeah, with razor wire. Wicked.
那可真不错
Well, that's something.
怎么了
What's going on?
我为什么在这
Why am I here?
嗯
Well, um…
小卡带你来的
That's Cass.
他是我们的朋友
He's our friend,
我们需要跟你谈谈
and we need to talk to you.
关于夏娃
about Eve.
夏娃吗
Eve?
关于夏娃我没什么好说的
I have nothing to say about Eve.
你确定吗
You sure about that?
我正努力躲着她 相信我
I'm trying to stay away from her. Believe me.
你的巢在哪
Where's your nest?
没了
Gone.
我抗拒不了了
I couldn't fight it anymore.
在我们脑子里
It's her voice…
一直有她的声音
in our heads…
她对我们做出的事
what it does to us.
所以他们离开了 又开始杀戮
So they left, started killing again.
但是你没有
But not you.
别表现的那么赞赏
Don't look so impressed.
我躲在一个地下室
I was hiding in a basement.
那可不怎么舒服
… not exactly club med.
你们不知道 不屈服是多么困难
You don't know how hard it is not to give in.
所有人都屈服了
Everyone gives in.
好吧 你这个双向通灵的能力
All right, so, this psychic two-way you got going,
这意味着你知道妖他妈在哪吗
does that mean you know where mom's camped out?
你拿我寻开心呢吧
You've got to be kidding me.
你要我告诉你她在哪
You want me to tell you where she is?
你知道她可能现在就在听我们说话
You do know she could be listening to us right now.
我差不多就是个摄像机了
I might as well be a video camera.
你们怎么想的啊
What are you thinking?
那么我们就不能奇袭了
So, we don't have the element of surprise.
我们还是要去
We're still going in.
你疯了
You're crazy.
我帮不了你们
I can't help you.
帮不了还是不想帮
Can't or won't?
很明显
Look, it's clear as day,
你还是在乎的
you still give a crap.
你不想杀戮
You don't want to kill,
你也不想让整个星球都完蛋
and you don't want this whole planet dead.
你真以为你能阻止她吗
You actually believe you can stop her?
就告诉我们她在哪吧
Just tell us where she is.
俄勒冈州 格兰茨帕斯
Grants Pass, Oregon.
现在她知道你们要去了
And now she knows you're coming.
那我们去看看吧
Well, let's go see.
等等
Hold on.
我告诉你们不是出于好心
I didn't tell you this out of the goodness of my heart.
我要点回报
I need something.
什么
What?
杀了我
Kill me.
丽诺尔 听我说
Lenore, look…
我们会把你锁起来 直到事情结束
We'll lock you down till this whole thing is over, okay?
证人保护 你很安全
Witness protection. You'll be safe.
你不明白 不是关于我的安全
You don't get it. It's not about that.
我才是危险人物
I'm dangerous.
我总是能听到她的声音
I hear her voice all the time.
你跟其他人不一样
You're not like the rest of them.
我跟他们一模一样
I'm exactly like them.
我吸血了
I fed.
我无法控制
I couldn't help it.
那女孩最多十六岁 萨姆
The girl couldn't have been more than 16, Sam.
有第一次就有第二次
I'll do it again.
我停不下来
I can't stop.
我再也无法自制了
Not anymore.
你必须杀了我
You have to.
- 求你 - 丽诺尔
- Please. - Lenore…
我们该行动了
We needed to move this along.
（俄勒冈州 格兰茨帕斯）
我还以为会是遍地僵尸呢
Well, I was expecting more "Zombieland, "
这里却一派祥和嘛
less "Pleasantville."
表面平静不代表真的平静
Just because it looks quiet don't mean it is,
特别是她还知道我们要来了
especially if she's got a clue we're coming.
如果她在这
Yeah, well, if she is here,
至少我们队还有个强力小翅膀
I'm glad we got Smitey McSmiterton on our squad.
好吧 我们从哪开始找
All right. Where do we start?
我需要一台电脑
I'm gonna need a computer.
好
All right.
我总算进到警方资料库了
I finally got the police database,
这玩意儿真不好使
no thanks to this.
我要的是「电脑」
I asked for a computer.
这就是电脑
It is a computer.
才不是 电脑是有按键的
No, a computer has buttons.
- 还要点别的吗 - 不用 谢谢
- Can I get you anything else? - No, we're good. Thanks.
有发现吗
Anything?
小打小闹 没什么怪事
Oh, nickel-and-dime stuff, nothing weird.
基本上是撞南墙了
Basically, dead end.
你觉得那个吸血鬼撒谎了吗
You think vampira was lying?
我去镇上搜搜 一下就好
I'll search the town. Give me a moment.
小卡 我们还能看到你哟
Cass, we can still see you.
是啊 我还在这
Yeah, I'm still here.
好吧 又不用你等我们
Okay, well, you don't have to wait on us.
你现在看上去像是在拉屎
Well, now it just looks like you're pooping.
- 有点不对劲 - 你卡住了啊
- Something's wrong. - What, are you stuck?
是受阻了
I'm blocked.
我没有法力了
I'm powerless.
你开玩笑吧
You're joking.
这镇上的什么东西
Something in this town is, uh…
在影响我
it's affecting me.
我想应该是夏娃
I assume it's Eve.
等等 妖他妈让你软了
So, wait. Mom's making you limp?
你可以这么说
Figuratively, yes.
- 怎么会 - 不知道 但她做到了
- How? - I don't know, but she is.
太好了 你失去法力
Oh, well, that's great, 'cause without your power,
基本上就是个穿着大衣的小宝宝
you're basically just a baby in a trench coat.
我觉得你伤到人家了
I think you hurt his feelings.
我好像查到了点东西
I got something here, maybe.
得到联邦资料库里才能找到
Had to go Federal to get it.
昨晚地方办事处给疾控中心打了通电话
Call went out from the Local Office to the C.D.C. Last night.
什么事
About what?
斯勒文医生
A Dr. Silver…
电话上报了一种他诊断不出来的疾病
called in an illness he couldn't identify.
病人是二十五岁的非裔美国人
Patient's a 25-year-old African-American.
名叫艾德·博莱斯
named Ed Bright.
没什么好查的
Well, that's not much to go on.
是我们唯一的线索了
Well, it's our only lead, so…
要饭的就别嫌饭馊了 我懂
So beggars can't be choosers. Right. I get it.
好吧 吃完走人吧
All right, well, let's finish up.
打扰下 斯勒文医生在吗
Excuse me. Hi. Uh, I-is Dr. Silver in today?
我朋友病得很重
My friend is very sick.
我有很疼的灼烧感
I have a, uh… painful burning sensation.
他不在 抱歉
Oh, well, he's out. Sorry.
你知道他在哪吗
Do you happen to know where he is?
他还没打电话来呢
He hasn't called in.
你还是自己找点药膏涂吧
You might want to find yourself some ointment.
哪有医生打电话给疾控中心
What kind of doctor calls the C.D.C.
第二天却开小差了
and then goes awol the very next day?
我们去看看吧
Let's have a look, shall we?
开锁要很长时间吗
Is this gonna take a long time?
怎么了
What is it?
是那个病人 艾德·博莱斯
It's the patient, Ed Bright.
哪有医生打电话给疾控中心
Well, what kind of doctor calls the C.D.C.
然后把黏糊糊的尸体藏在自己的棚子里
and then stashes the gooey corpse in his shed?
我不明白到底怎么回事
I don't understand what's happening here.
我倒是知道该怎么处理尸体
Well, I know one thing about the body,
我们需要煤油
we need some kerosene.
看 斯勒文医生 他老婆和两个儿子
Here. Dr. Silver. Wife, two sons.
你们好啊
Hi, there.
你好
Hi.
你们是谁
Who are you?
便装日吗 探员们
It casual Friday, agents?
我们就在几英里外办案
We were on a case a few miles out.
接到个电话就过来了
We got a call to come here.
那么你呢 来干什么
So, how about you? What's your business?
斯勒文医生是我的朋友
Oh, dr. Silver's a friend of mine.
听说他今天没上班
Heard he didn't show up for work today,
所以来看看他是不是病了
So I thought I'd stop by and see if he's sick.
没病 失踪了
Not sick. Missing.
失踪 谁说的
Missing? Says who?
我说的 空房子 没打包行李
Says me … empty house, no bags packed,
车还在门口
car still in the driveway.
你们怎么知道的
Well, how'd you get on this?
说来话长
Oh, it's a long story.
跟你说 你最好发布个全境通告
Tell you what … why don't you put out an a.P.B.?
我们回警局再交流 怎样
We'll compare notes down at the station. Sound good?
好的
Uh, yeah, yeah.
- 当然 - 感谢
- Sure. - Obliged.
好一个金蝉脱壳啊
Wow, talk about talking out of your butt.
赶紧吧 你个小白痴
Yeah. Just hurry, you idjit.
一个失踪的医生和一个烂掉的病人
So we got a missing doctor and an oozy patient, huh?
扑朔迷离啊
Yeah. Plot thickens.
咱们去看看艾德的室友有什么要说的
Well, let's go see what Ed's roommates have to say.
艾德·博莱斯有没有兄弟
Does Ed Bright have a brother?
没 怎么了
No. Why?
那么那个就不是他双胞胎兄弟了
Then that's not his twin.
怎么 变形怪么
So, what … shifter?
我不知道那是什么
I don't know what we're looking at.
好吧 迪恩和我进去
All right, Dean and me are gonna go in.
你俩呆在这里看门
You two stay here and watch the door.
有东西跑出来 就开枪
Something comes out, shoot it.
最好用银子弹
Yeah, best guess … silver bullets.
我不太会用火器
I'm fairly unpracticed with firearms.
你知道什么人才嗷嗷的吗
You know who whines?
小宝宝
Babies.
什么都别碰
Okay. Don't touch anything.
这里
Hey, hey, back here.
过来
Come here.
告诉我们 怎么回事
Talk to us. What is this?
艾德
Ed?
- 艾德 发生了什么 - 什么
- Ed, what's going on? - What?
我不是艾德
I'm not Ed.
我怎么了
What's wrong with me?
没什么 你很好
Uh, nothing. You're okay.
你没事 我们会帮你的
You're okay, all right? We're gonna get you help.
我有些问题
Let me ask you something.
我
Do I …
我们所有人
Do all of us …
是不是都变成艾德了
Do we look like Ed?
什么 不
What? No.
不 不 当然没有
No, no, no, no, no, no, of course not.
你发烧了 产生幻觉了
You, uh … you have a fever. You're hallucinating.
马歇尔 到底怎么回事
Marshall, Marshall, hey, what happened here?
我要死了吗
Am I gonna die?
不 你不会死的
No. You're not gonna die, okay?
快告诉我们 这很重要
Now, you need to talk to us. It's important.
艾德感觉不舒服 所以我带他去看医生
Ed was feeling bad, so I took him to the doctor.
我想我们现在都病了
I think now we're all sick.
还用你说
You think?
在你和艾德病之前
And before you got sick and before Ed got sick,
你们有做过什么 去过哪里
Did you do anything? Did you go anywhere?
集中精神
Hey, need you to focus for me.
我不知道
I don't know.
某个酒吧
Some bar.
酒吧 什么酒吧
A bar? What bar?
好像在八号街
Eighth street, I guess.
八号街
Eighth street.
酒吧里发生什么了吗
Um, and did anything happen at the bar?
看到了什么 遇见了什么人吗
D-did you see anything? Did you meet anyone?
救护车马上就到
Look, an ambulance is on the way.
一个女孩
A girl.
一个女孩 然后呢
A girl? Okay. And?
白衣女孩
A girl in white.
好的
Good. Okay.
白衣女孩做了什么 马歇尔
What did the girl in white do, Marshall?
她对艾德做过什么
What did she do to Ed?
马歇尔
Marshall!
我不明白
I don't get it.
一群无名小卒醒来发现成变形怪了
What, a bunch of regular joes wake up shifters?
坑爹呢这是
What the hell?
变形怪一般是家族遗传
Shifters usually run in families.
这情况像是传染
This looks like an infection.
你俩没碰过什么吧
Nobody touched nothing?
今晚我要用滴露洗澡
Well, I'm bathing in purell tonight.
他说他们遇见了一个女孩
So, he said they met a girl.
肯定是夏娃
It's got to be eve.
她为什么要这么做
But why would she do this?
怪物之母 生怪物
Mommy monster. Make more.
不 不 小卡问到点儿上了
No, no, no, no, Cass has got a good point.
如果她要建一支变形怪军团
I mean, if she's gonna make a shifter army,
为什么要这种病到小命就快交代了的
why make one that's this sick, gooey, and dying?
把这加到未解之谜全书里吧
Add that to the pile of crap that don't make sense.
我们要去那酒吧吗
So, should we hit the bar?
即便治安官是个二货
Well, the sheriff's a mook, but still …
但应该会注意到这么多失踪人口吧
You'd think he'd notice this many missing folks.
这里有个吸血鬼
We got a vamp over here.
哦不 是个死灵
Nope. Scratch that. We got a wraith.
怎么回事
What the hell?
什么东西有尖牙还有手刀
What has teeth and a spike?
这辈子没见过
Never seen that in my life.
真好 夏娃开始搞杂交了
Oh, great. So eve's making hybrids now?
看起来像 问题是为什么
Looks like. The question is, why?
我是说 她为什么想要
I mean, what does she want with a …
这玩意叫什么
What do you call these?
恭喜你 你发现的 自己想名字
Well, congrats. You discovered it. You get to name it.
杰佛逊飞船（美国摇滚团体）
Jefferson starships.
因为他们很恐怖
Because they're horrible…
并且很难干倒
And hard to kill.
看起来整个酒吧的人都被变成了
Looks like the whole bar has been turned into the …
杰佛逊飞船
Jefferson starships.
好吧 但为什么所有飞船仔都死了
Fine. But why are all the…Starships dead?
说不准 不过
I can't say, but…
他们好像都烧起来了
It looks like they all burned up.
烧起来 就像
Burned up? Like …
就像发高烧 得流感一样
Like a high fever, like the flu.
这里到底是怎么回事
What the hell's going on here?
这里所有的怪物都染上莫他巴病毒（出自电影《恐怖地带》）了吗
Does every monster in this town have the motaba virus?
把手举起来
Hands where I can see them!
这是一场误会
Now, this is not what it looks like.
我们是联邦探员
Look, we're the feds.
是吗 联邦探员可不准干这些事
Yeah? Well, feds are not allowed to do this.
拷上 转身
Cuff 'em. Turn around.
如果我们能打个电话
Listen, if we can make a phone call,
就能把一切解释清楚
we can straighten this all out.
解释大屠杀 我倒想见识一下
Straighten out a massacre? I'd like to see you try.
杰佛逊飞船
J-jefferson starships!
迪恩 等等
Dean, wait!
我得说
Well, I'll say this …
你是我这一天看到的最完整的样品
You're the healthiest-looking specimen I've seen all day.
我吃维他命
I take my vitamins.
你能告诉我们到底怎么回事吗
So, you want to tell us what's going on here?
你们是 夏娃的清洁工吗
So, you boys are, uh, Eve's cleaning crew?
是吗 你们
Is that it? You, uh …
你们来处理尸体
you come around to clean up the bodies,
确保秘密不会泄露 是吧
make sure the word doesn't get out, huh?
所以你们抓走了医生
Is that why you snatched up the doctor?
你只是在浪费时间
You're so wasting your time.
你这头蠢猪
You stupid head of cattle.
还有飞船仔
More starships.
呆在这里
Stay here.
你们是斯勒文医生的孩子
You're Dr. Silver's boys.
别担心 我们放你们出来
All right, don't worry. We're gonna get you out of here, okay?
- 钥匙 - 好的
- Uh, uh, keys? - Yeah.
听着
Look…
我们不会伤害你们
we're not gonna hurt you.
我叫萨姆 那是我哥 迪恩
My name is Sam. And that's my brother, Dean.
那些警察 他们不会回来了 永远不会
Those cops … they're not coming back, ever.
你们叫什么
What are your names?
我叫乔 他是莱恩
Joe. This is Ryan.
莱恩你好
Hiya, Ryan. How you doing?
自从我们被抓之后
He won't talk,
他就不肯说话了
not since they came for us.
好吧 乔 我们会帮你们把
All right, listen, Joe, we're gonna get you.
手铐解开
out of those handcuffs.
但是你也知道现在的状况 对吧
But you understand what's going on around here, don't you?
首先 我们得确认你们是人类
So first we got to make sure you're you.
你们要怎么做
How you gonna do that?
需要做一些 测试
Well, there's a few, uh, dozen tests.
好吧 开始吧
Okay, let's get started.
这点手段就能让我开口吗
Y-you really think that's gonna make me talk?
总有办法治得了你
Something will.
找到了两个饥肠辘辘的小孩
Got a couple of hungry human boys here.
走吧 小子们
Come on, guys.
你俩从未听他们说起过
So, you two never heard them talk…
什么母亲 或者
about a mother or…
一个叫夏娃的人
someone named Eve?
那里只有我和莱恩
It was just me and Ryan in there.
你们的亲人呢
And your folks?
警察说下一个就是我们
Cops said we were next.
他们说我们是食物
They said we were food.
你还有其他家人吗
You have any other family?
有一个叔叔在梅利特
An uncle in Meritt.
在哪里 镇外十五英里处吗
Meritt. What's that, like 15 miles outside of town?
好的 我们送你们过去
Okay, we'll get you there.
迪恩 方便说两句吗
Dean. Can I have a word?
眼下我们得找到夏娃
We need to find Eve now.
对 去吧
Yeah. Go.
我和萨姆就是去开个小差
Me and Sam just got to make a milk run.
不 我们需要你们的帮助
No, we need your help here.
你给我憋着
Hold your water.
我们很快就回来
We'll be back in a few.
迪恩 迪恩
Dean, Dean.
很多人的生命都危在旦夕 不只是他俩
Millions of lives are at stake here, not just two.
- 专注一点 - 你开玩笑吗
- Stay focused. - Are you kidding?
还有更重要的任务
There's a greater purpose here.
我告诉你
You know what?
我已经厌倦了
I-I'm getting a little sick and tired.
这些更重要的任务
of the greater purposes, okay?
我现在就想
I think what I'd like to do right now.
救那两个孩子 如果你不介意的话
is save a couple of kids, if you don't mind.
我们马上就回来
We'll catch up.
好吧 我们走
Okay, guys, let's go.
走吧
Come on.
你应该休息一会儿
Hey. You should get some rest.
他们不会去太久的
They won't take long.
说不准
You don't know that.
他们一路上可能会发现更多任性的孤儿
They may find more wayward orphans along the way.
少傲娇了你
Oh, don't get cute.
好吧
Right.
请原谅我用「讽刺」的方法
Pardon me for highlighting.
来突显两兄弟危险又影响大局的
their crippling and dangerous empathetic response.
同情行为
with "sarcasm."
不应该让他俩离开的
It was a bad idea, letting them go.
乖啦
Come on.
温家双煞不可能袖手旁观
You don't let Sam and Dean Winchester do squat.
他们都是做该做的事 你知道的
They do what they got to. You know that.
反正我们要想找到夏娃
Anyway, we want Eve,
首先得知道她在哪里
we need coordinates.
我们要么就在这里继续抱怨
So, we can stand here bellyaching,
要么就去给那小子来个满清十大酷刑
or we can go poke that pig till he squeals.
意下如何
Thoughts?
她现在能看见你们
You know, she can see you right now.
你们却在惹她生气
And you're just making her mad.
让那个贱人来找我啊
Then tell the bitch to come get me.
我要单独和他呆五分钟
I need five minutes alone with him.
为什么
What for?
小卡
Cass…
你的法力没有了
your batteries are dead.
给我五分钟
Give me five minutes.
好的 好吧
All right. Fine.
夏娃在巴克利街二十五号
Eve's at 25 buckley street.
你可以打给萨姆和迪恩了
You can call Sam and Dean.
酷刑审问哈
Rigorous interrogation, huh?
我们知道她的位置了
Well, we got a location.
现在我们只需要接近她 然后伺机下手
Now we just got to get close enough to take a shot.
好的
All right. Well…
每人一颗
Let's all take one.
装上膛 要一枪一准
Load 'em up. Make 'em count.
我勒个去
You got to be kidding me.
她一直在那里啊
She's been in there the whole time?
她怎么会放我们进去啊
Why'd she ever let us in?
还放我们出来
Or out.
有一个办法能知道
Well, there's one way to find out.
就那么慢悠悠走进去么
What, just stroll in?
我们都不知道哪些是人 哪个是她
We don't know who's human or who's her.
有个办法能把她引出来
Well, there's one way to draw her out.
- 我和萨姆进去 - 迪恩
- Me and Sam will go in. - Dean…
我们要是没机会开枪 那就得靠你们俩了
Look, we don't get a shot off, you two better.
就这么蛮干啊
That's the plan?
是啊 就这样
Yeah. Pretty much.
至少还算简单明了
Well, at least it ain't complicated.
咋整
Now what?
不妙 不妙
Crap. Crap.
很不妙
Crap.
飞船仔
Starships?
没错
Yeah.
这个餐馆里就没有
Is there anybody in this diner.
不是食人妖魔的吗
that is not a flesh-eating monster?
有 咱哥俩
Uh, me and you.
好吧 那我们快走吧
Okay, well, let's get the hell out of here.
- 好啊 - 两份特餐 是吗
- Shall we? - Two specials, right?
不 不是我们点的 我们正要走呢
Uh, no, that's not for us. We were just heading out.
别这么没礼貌 萨姆
Now, that would be rude, Sam.
我猜猜
Let me guess.
你是夏娃
Eve.
幸会
Pleasure.
我们干嘛不出去聊聊
Why don't we step outside, chat?
何必 这里没人打扰
Why? This is private.
凤凰灰烬 挺厉害啊
Phoenix ash. I'm impressed.
你们肯定费了很大事才找到
I bet you had to go a long way for that.
可不是
You have no idea.
把这些销毁 谢谢
Destroy these. Thank you.
放松点
Relax.
我不是来打架的
I'm not here to fight.
对 只是来集结全球所有妖魔鬼怪的
No, just to rally every freak on the planet,
带些个肉虫王 山寨蜘蛛人
bring in khan worms and… and half-assed spider-men.
还有龙
and dragons.
说真的 姑娘 还带龙来
Really, sister? Dragons?
我是搬出来一些老怪物 我需要帮助
So, I dusted off some of the old classics. I needed help.
帮你干嘛
With what?
毁掉这个星球吗
Tearing apart the planet?
你们误解我了
You misunderstand me.
我从没想要那样做
I never wanted that,
一开始没想
not at first.
我喜欢我们的协议
I liked our arrangement.
什么协议
What arrangement?
自然界的秩序
The natural order.
我的孩儿们转化一些人类
My children turned a few of you.
你们去猎杀一些我的孩儿 我挺高兴的
You hunted a few of them. I was happy.
好啊 那什么变了
Okay. So what changed?
我的孩儿们 都是你们俩害得
My children, no thanks to you,
开始被人绑架 被折磨
started getting kidnapped and tortured,
甚至我的长子们
even my firstborns.
我被逼卷入此事
I was pushed into this.
毕竟 妈妈总会保护她的孩子
After all, a mother defends her children.
你不是吧
Really?
要用「年度最佳妈妈」来为自己辩护吗
You're gonna use the "Mother of the year" defense?
就你
You?
碰巧是真的
It happens to be true.
这样吧
Know what?
如果我变成这样
Maybe you'll believe it if I look.
你们就会相信我了
a little more like this.
你个贱货
Oh, you bitch.
她为了保护你们而牺牲 对吧
She died to protect you, didn't she?
看见没
See?
你们也明白母爱
You understand a mother's love.
- 我也一样 - 好吧 你给老子听着
- I'm no different. - All right, you know what?
谈话到此结束
This conversation's over.
如果要杀我们 就请动手
If you're gonna kill us, kill us.
你们
You?
不
No.
我只想要克劳力的命
It's Crowley I want dead.
那你下手太慢了
Well, you're too late there.
那个英国佬几个月前已经死了
That little limey mook roasted months ago.
克劳力还活着
Crowley's alive.
不可能
That's impossible.
我从每个被他折磨的孩子眼中
I see his face through the eyes.
看到了他的脸
of every child he strings up and skins.
知道他为什么要伤害我的孩子吗
Any idea why he's hurting my babies?
他想要炼狱 对吧
He wants purgatory, right?
位置神马的
Location, location, location.
他是那么跟你们说的吗
Is that what he told you?
是为了灵魂
It's about the souls.
灵魂怎么了
Well, what about them?
它们是力量 你个纯洁的小笨蛋
They're power, you simple little monkey.
是燃料
Fuel.
每一个灵魂都是最好的核反应堆
Each soul a beautiful, little nuclear reactor.
收集起来 你就拥有了太阳
Put them together, you have the sun.
想想 地狱之王拥有了这个
Now, think what the king of hell could do.
未开发的巨大油井 他会做什么
with that vast, untapped oil well…
他会变得多么强大
How powerful he'd be.
克劳力现在想偷走我的东西
Now Crowley wants to siphon off my supply.
折磨我的孩子帮他达到目的
and torture my children to do it?
好吧 老虎不发威当我病猫
Okay, fine. I'll quit playing nice.
我就转化所有人
I'll turn you all.
每一个灵魂 归我所有
Every soul … mine.
当所有灵魂都归我的时候
Let's see how hot his hell burns.
我们看看他还能得意到几时
when everyone comes to me.
这是他自找的
He asked for it.
据我所知 地球上也有个几十亿人吧
You know, last I checked, there are a few billion of us.
你的计划需要费些时日
That plan might take a while.
你认为我来这里做什么的
What exactly do you think I'm doing here?
我在打造完美的怪兽
I'm building the perfect beast.
等等
Wait a second.
我们
All those …
我们发现的这些东西
all those things we've been finding.
这叫做内测
Call it beta testing.
我觉得你的配方有点不对啊
Well, I think your formula might be a little off.
它们到处自相残杀
They're imploding all over town.
是有一些次品
Ohh, there were a few unfortunate failures.
但是我终于成功了
But I eventually got it right.
安静 聪明 不易察觉
Quiet, smart, inconspicuous.
一天之内就可以遍布整个小镇
It can spread through a whole town in under a day.
最精彩的地方是
Oh, and the best part …
他一直都在你们身边
You've been with it the whole time.
什么
What?
是的 你们就是他的最终关卡
Yes, you were the final test.
我当然要确定他能否
I had to see if it could.
神不知鬼不觉逃过猎魔人的眼睛
slip past hunters undetected, of course.
是小莱恩
Little Ryan.
乔
Joe?
莱恩
Ryan?
你们貌似不开心
You look upset.
说句让你们舒心的话
If it makes you feel any better,
莱恩注定能骗的过你们
Ryan was bound to work on you.
任性的小孤儿…
Little wayward orphan…
就像你们一样
Like yourselves.
你们现在已经无能为力了
There's nothing you can do about it now.
所以还是谈谈吧
So let's talk.
没什么好谈的
Nothing to say.
这么说可不对
Well, that's where you're wrong.
我有一个提议
I have an offer to propose.
克劳力…
Crowley…
踪迹难觅 这你们都知道
As you know, not so easy to find.
所以不如这样…
So, here's the deal…
你们去找到他…
You find him…
把他带来见我…
Bring him to me…
我就饶你们一命
I let you live.
免了
Pass.
- 迪恩 - 萨姆 不行
- Dean… - Sam, no.
答案是不行
The answer is no.
说得好像你还有别的选择似的
You say that like you have another option.
也许有 也许没有
Maybe I do, maybe I don't.
是嘛
You think?
那我就彻底断了你们的念想
Well, so much for your plan "B".
你一定在想「我为什么会如此软弱」
And you, wondering, "Why so flaccid?"
卡西迪奥 我比你年长
I'm older than you, Castiel.
我知道天使的死穴
I know what makes angels tick.
只要我在 你就把自己当做
As long as I'm around, consider yourself…
废物吧
unplugged.
为我卖命吧
Work for me.
条件很优厚呦
It's a good deal.
追加福利 饶你们的朋友也不死
Bonus… I won't kill your friends.
听着
All right, look,
过去几个月里 我们一直在为个恶棍卖命
The last few months, we've been working for an evil dick.
我们可不想改为投靠一个巫婆
We're not about to sign up for an evil bitch.
我们不会与恶魔合作
We don't work with demons.
也不会与怪物合作
We don't work with monsters.
如果你会因此杀了我们 尽管动手吧
And if that means you got to kill us, then kill us!
或者…
Or…
我可以转化你们…
I turn you…
到时你们就任我摆布了
and you do what I want anyway.
打死我都不会同意
Beat me with a wire hanger, answer's still no.
不要
Don't…
逼我
test me.
你咬我呀
Bite me.
- 不要 - 迪恩
- No! - Dean!
凤凰灰烬
Phoenix ash.
一颗子弹…
One shell…
加一盎司威士忌…
One ounce of whiskey…
一饮而尽
Down the hatch.
之后会散发点腐气
Little musty on the afterburn.
再见了 妈妈
Call you later, mom.
闭眼
Shut your eyes!
以后应该多带你参加猎魔行动
We got to take you on more monster hunts.
小卡…
Hey, Cass, um…
迪恩正血流不止
Dean's bleeding pretty good.
我觉得她把我转化成杰佛逊飞船了
I think she turned me into a Jefferson starship.
你能帮我一并恢复吗
Could you clear that up, too?
好了 没事了
All right, we're good.
我们得赶紧走了
We got to go. Now.
去哪里
Where?
那个孩子
The kid.
那个小孩 也是怪物之一
The little kid … he's one of them.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
小卡 我懂 你告诉过我
Yeah, I know, Cass. You told me, all right?
快走吧
Let's just go.
我们杀了那个巫婆 却还是让她得逞了
So, we kill the wicked witch, and she still wins.
目前为止他们可能已经转化了半个镇的人
I mean, they could have turned half the town by now.
不许吐槽
Don't say it.
找到他们了
Found them.
又是谁把他们杀死的呢
Well, who ganked them?
是恶魔
Demons.
你怎么想
So, what do you think?
我认为如果不是因为受了指使
I think that demons don't give a crap.
恶魔才不会鸟什么怪物兄弟呢
about monster tweens unless they're told to.
那你觉得她说的是实话吗
So, you think she was telling the truth?
什么实话
The truth about what?
她说克劳力还活着
She said that Crowley's still kicking.
但我已经烧了他的遗骨 怎么…
But I burned his bones. How c…
她肯定吗
Was she certain?
听上去很有把握
Sounded pretty sure.
据她所说
According to her,
克劳力仍在某处残害着她的后裔
Crowley's still waterboarding her kids somewhere.
我糊涂了
I don't understand.
他可是个狡猾的王八蛋
Well, he's a crafty son of a bitch.
而我是个天使 我马上就去调查此事
I'm an angel. I'll look into it immediately.
小卡
Cass!
别忘了把调查结果告诉我们
Let us know what you find out!
怎么了 怎么了
What? What?
克劳力怎么可能逃脱了呢
How did Crowley get away?
小卡不可能犯那样的错误
I mean, it's not like Cass to make mistakes like that,
除非…
unless…
除非怎样
Unless what?
除非他有意为之
Unless he meant to.
鲍比 你居然怀疑小卡
Bobby, this is Cass we're talking about.
你相信吗
Do you believe this?
萨姆
Sam?
大概是我们想多了
Look, it's probably nothing.
只是…
It's just…
你说得对 大概是我们想多了
You know what? You're right. It's… it's probably nothing.
小卡 说真的…
Really, Cass…
事情越来越荒唐了
This is getting ridiculous.
我还要为你擦屁股到什么时候
How many times am I gonna have to clean up your messes?